

Career Objective

As a systems analysis and development major at one of Brazil's top universities, my dream career since before I entered high school has been to pursue a **Python Developer** role. In 2016, I began my journey in web development as a competitor in the Brazilian Computer Olympics challenge. Now, I work as as a Python Developer using Django and am seeking new opportunities. Raised for several years in the U.S. and with a record of stellar contribution working remotely, I am well equipped to implement a client's next concept into an active solution.

Employment History

Software Developer, Peppertools.com.br, Hybrid

JULY 2018 — PRESENT

Fixed computers and wrote g-code to increase tool production.

Used three management systems: one with object-oriented PHP, another with Python using flask framework and an object-relational mapping library, and the final transitioned with Django due to scalability issues.

Django Developer, InProcesses.io, Remote

JUNE 2022 — PRESENT

Side project working as a back-end and mobile developer with React Native (Expo) and Django Rest Framework.

Full Stack Developer, Eucompro.com, Remote

JULY 2022 — PRESENT

Worked on an auction and classified site, using PHP CRM, git, hosting server, Cloudflare, translation, web design, business plan, marketing.

Junior Developer, Beytech IT Solutions, Remote

MARCH 2022 — JUNE 2022

Assisted with database and FTP server files migration and fixing other WordPress website issues.

Worked on a Django project whose main goal was to integrate with Bitrix24 issuing a Brazilian form of payment called 'boleto', using Django Rest Framework

Projects

WordPress - E-commerce, Bragança Paulista

JUNE 2020 — OCTOBER 2020

Built an epoxy selling site with WordPress using woo-commerce, Elementor, and social plugins.

www.epoxibraganca.com.br

Startup Site - B2MO, Bragança Paulista

OCTOBER 2019 — NOVEMBER 2020

Details

Avenida José Gomes da Rocha Leal, Bragança Paulista, 12900-300, Brazil 55 11 92002 3609 lauropimentel12@gmail.com GitHub Linkedin

NATIONALITY

Brazilian

Education

System Analysis & Development, Federal Institute of Brazil, Bragança Paulista

AUGUST 2021 - AUGUST 2024

Skills

SQL

Python - Flask / Django
JavaScript - React/ React native
PHP
HTML & CSS - BootStrap
Git
SQLite
MySQL
WordPress
Kotlin
C
PostgreSQL

Relevant Courses

CS50X, Harvard University
CS50W, Harvard University
Android Development w/ Kotlin,
SENAI/CEBRAE
Full Stack Flask Developer,
Pirple.com
PHP Course, Sololearn
PHP CRUD, Udemy
Swift, Sololearn

Extracurricular Activities

Startup business repairing iPhones

Languages

Portuguese

English

Built a simple site with PHPMailer, OOP, and JS, for a startup promoting their work on sustainable energy.

b2motech.com.br

ONU - European Cultural Heritage, Bragança Paulista

AUGUST 2018 — DECEMBER 2018

Built a WordPress website for a European Cultural Heritage school's fair with each group posting a European country.

No longer hosted due to financial reasons. So It's freely open on GitHub.

Covid-19 - Project, Bragança Paulista

JUNE 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2020

Worked on a Coronavirus information project with a group:

Debugged and developed in JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and deployed with Heroku.